Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Legal: Logo, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 14)
    - Legal: San Diego People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 15)
    - Letters, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 16)
    - Letters: Circulation Complaints, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 17)
    - Letters: Complaints on Edit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 18)
    - Letters: Editorial, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 19)
    - Letters: Kajinski, Billie, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 20)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 21)
    - Letters: Reports, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 22-23)
    - Life, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 24)
    - Liquor Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 25)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Agencies, Advertisers, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 26)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: South St. Seaport: June 25, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 27)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Bloomingdale's: September 23, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 28)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Nashville: October 9-10, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 29)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Bloomingdale's: October 14, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 30)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Dallas Party: November 18, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 31)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Russell Party: Night in Casablanca: November 24, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 32)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Wassail Feast: Detroit: December 10, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 33)
    - Madison Avenue, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 34)
    - Magazines, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 35)
    - Magazine Committee Meeting: September 30-October 1, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 1)
    - Magazine Committee Meeting: January 5, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 2)
    - Magazine Development, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 3)
    - Magazine Group: Finance and Developing, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 4)
    - Mailings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 5)
    - Mailings: Others, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 6)
    - Media Industry Newsletter [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 7)
    - Mediamark Research Inc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 8)
    - Meetings: April 16, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 9)
    - Meetings: Board Managers Meeting: October 6-8, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 10)
    - Meetings: ABC Annual Meeting: November 4-5, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Briskman, Ira, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Burgheim, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Crawford, Clare, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 14-16)
    - Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Davidson, Ralph, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: D'Onofrio, Pat: Share Of Market Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Elliman, Don, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: Fisler, Bob, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Goltra, Libby, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Grum, Clifford, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Grunwald, Henry, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Gunn, Larry, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 30)
    - Memoranda: Heiskell, Andrew, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 31)
    - Memoranda: Himmelfarb, Debbie, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 32)
    - Memoranda: Karageorge, Penelope, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 33)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Arthur, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 34)
    - Memoranda: King, Charlie, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 35)
    - Memoranda: Kyle, Bob, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 36)
    - Memoranda: Labich, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 37)
    - Memoranda: Legal, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda: List, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: Marketing Services, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 40)
    - Memoranda: McClusky, Jim, 1981 (Offsite-box 2985, Folder 41)
    - Memoranda: Meigher, Chris, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Miller, Bill, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Motta, Tony, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Mulcahy, Eileen, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Munro, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Nunes, Lucy (Freelance), 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 7-8)
    - Memoranda: Owen, Mike, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 9-10)
    - Memoranda: Promotion, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Publicity, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Roth, Frank, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Rueffer, Terry, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Ryan, Pat, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Schiller, Clark, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Sidey, Hugh, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Slovinsky, Lou, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Stoklos, Mary, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Sutton, Kelso, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 22-23)
    - Memoranda: Thorkilsen, Eric, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 24-25)
    - Memoranda: Znachko, Mike, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 26)
    - Monthly Reports: Ad Sales, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 27)
    - Movie Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 28)
    - Music Special Issue, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 29)
      1 phonograph record; 7 in. Label on envelope: Addressed to "People - Dick Durrell". Label on Side A: "JBW Records, 'People' by Jerry Westerman". Label on Side B: "JBW Records, 'Mountain to Climb' by Jerry Westerman".
    - National Enquirer, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 30)
    - National Golf Links, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 31)
    - National Star, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 32)
    - New York Management Meetings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 33)
    - New York Times, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 34)
    - Out of Town Schedule, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 35)
    - Parties, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 36)
    - Parties: Christmas Pour, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 37)
    - People to People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 38)
    - People Poll Issue, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 39)
    - People Shopper, 1981 (Offsite-box 2986, Folder 40)
    - People Spring 1981 Fisler Poly (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 1)
    - Permissions, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 2)
    - Personnel, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 3)
    - Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Photo Context, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 4)
    - Photo Exhibit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 5)
    - Photo Exhibit: St. Louis: April 6, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 6)
    - Photo Exhibit: Cleveland: May 6, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 7)
    - Photo Exhibit: Pittsburgh: June 15, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 8)
    - Photo Exhibit: Minneapolis: July 13, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 9)
    - Photo Exhibit: Chicago: July 3, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 10)
    - PIB, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 11)
    - Positioning, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 12)
    - Postal Service, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 13)
    - Posters, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 14)
    - Presentations, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 15)
    - President's Lunch, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 16)
    - Price Tests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 17)
    - Print Order, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 18)
    - Print Order: Plants, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 19)
    - Production, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 20)
    - Production Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 21)
    - Promotion: Air, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 22)
    - Promotion: Consumer Circulation, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 23-24)
    - Promotion: Director Applications, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 25)
    - Promotion: General, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 26)
    - Promotion: Holland and Callaway, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 27)
    - Promotion: Print, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 28)
    - Promotion: Weekly Letter, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 29)
    - Pub Letter, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 30)
    - Public Place, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 31)
    - Publicity: Air, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 32)
    - Publicity: General, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 33)
    - Publisher's Lunch, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 34)
    - Raises, 1981 (Offsite-box 2987, Folder 35)
    - Rates, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 1)
    - Rates Increase, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 2)
    - Reader's Digest, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 2)
    - Rebates: Advertising Complaints, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 3)
    - Reprints, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 4)
    - Regional, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 5)
    - Renewal Space Credit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 6)
    - Reprints, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 7)
    - Research, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 8)
    - Research: Focus Groups, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 9)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Toronto, Detroit, Washington D.C.: February 17-20, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 10)
    - Research: Focus Groups: St. Louis, Milwaukee, Cleveland: April 5-8, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 11)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Los Angeles, Phoenix: May 18-19, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 12)
    - Research: Men's Changing Roles, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 13)
    - Research: Newsweek Comparative, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 14)
    - Research: Reader Panel, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 15)
    - Research: Reader Perception Study, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 16)
    - Research: Subscriber Research, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 17)
    - Result Stories, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 18)
    - Sales Figures, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 19)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 20-21)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 22)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 23)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 24)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Himmelfarb, Debbie, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 25)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Marketing Services Research, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 26)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 27)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Promotion, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 28)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 29)
    - Screenings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 30)
    - "Search For Alexander", 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 31-32)
    - "Search For Alexander": Chicago: May 14, 1981 (Offsite-box 2988, Folder 33)
    - "Search For Alexander": Boston: November 22, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 1)
    - Selling Areas Marketing Inc. (SAMI), 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 2)
    - Serialization, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 4)
    - Simmons Market Research Bureau (SMRB), 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 5)
    - Space, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 6)
    - Special Editions, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 7)
    - Special Units, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 8)
    - Speeches: Others, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Requests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 11)
    - Starch, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 12)
    - Steer Meetings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 13)
    - Steering Committee: Research Programs for Magazines, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 14)
    - Store Checks by Salesmen, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 15)
    - Subscriptions, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 16)
    - Subscriptions: Tests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 17)
    - Supermarket News, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 18)
    - Syndication, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 19)
    - Television and Television Shows, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 20)
    - Tests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 21)
    - Time, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 22)
    - Time Distribution Services: A & P, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 23)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checkout, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 24)
    - Time Distribution Services: Clinics, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 25)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 26)
    - Time Distribution Services: Direct Sell to Chains, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 27)
    - Time Distribution Services: Draw, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 28)
    - Time Distribution Services: General, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 29)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 30)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Meeting: April 13-16, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 31)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Meeting: July 12-16, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 32-33)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Meeting: October 14, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 34)
    - Time Distribution Services: Newsstand, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 35)
    - Time Distribution Services: On Line Media, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 36)
    - Time Distribution Services: People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 37)
    - Time Distribution Services: Personnel, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 38)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking Stories Covered Weekly, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 39)
    - Time Distribution Services: Sports Clinic, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 40)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 41)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Book and Record Stores [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 42)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Box Stores, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 43)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Drug Stores [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 44)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Jewel Stores, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 45)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Kroger, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 46)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Safeway, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 47)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Sav-On, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 48)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Stop and Shop: Louis Banks, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 49)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weekly and Monthly Reports, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 50)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weekly Regional Managers Sales Estimates, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 51)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1981 (Offsite-box 2989, Folder 52)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Charles Levy Circulation Company, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Late Delivery, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 2)
    - Time/Life Books, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 3)
    - Trades, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 4)
    - Travel Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 5)
    - Trips: Company Plane, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 6)
    - TV Guide, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 7)
    - United Way, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 8)
    - Us, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 9)
    - Us: Circulation, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 10)
    - Us: Promotion, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 11)
    - Us: Publicity, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 12)
    - Us: Sales Figures, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 13)
    - Vacations, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Meetings, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 16-17)
    - Woman's Day, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 18)
    - Woman's World, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 19)
    - Women, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 20)
    - Women's Books, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 21)
    - Year End Guesstimate, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 22)
    - Year End Issue, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 23)
    - Young & Rubicam: Promotion, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 24)
    - Branch Offices: Atlanta, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 25)
    - Branch Offices: Boston, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 26)
    - Branch Offices: Chicago, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 27)
    - Branch Offices: Dallas, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 28)
    - Branch Offices: Detroit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 29)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 30)
    - Branch Offices: Memphis, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 31)
    - Branch Offices: Minneapolis, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 32)
    - Branch Offices: New York, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 33)
    - Branch Offices: San Francisco, 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 34)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1981 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 35)
    - Account Responsibilities, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 36)
    - Ad Age, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 37)
    - Ad Council, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 38)
    - Ad Director's Memoranda [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 39)
    - Admarc, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 40)
    - Advertising Age, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 41)
    - Advertising Records, Etc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 42)
    - Advertising Research Foundation [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 43)
    - Advertising/Edit Ratio, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 44)
    - Adweek, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 45)
    - Affirmative Action, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 46)
    - Agency Review, 1982 (Offsite-box 2990, Folder 47-48)
    - Airline Subs [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 1)
    - Airport Sales, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 2)
    - Alternate Delivery, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 3)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 5)
    - Apparel Category [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 6)
    - A.R.A. [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 7)
    - Audience Figures, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 8)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 9)
    - Automotive Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 10)
    - Awards, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 11)
    - Bleed [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 12)
    - Blood Bank Drive: April 6-9, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 13)
    - Books, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 14)
    - Budget: 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 15)
    - Budget: 1983, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 16)
    - Budget: Ad Sales, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 17)
    - Budget: Circulation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 18)
    - Budget: Direct Mail [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 19)
    - Budget: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 20)
    - Budget: Meeting: November 18, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 21)
    - Budget: Production, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 22)
    - Budget: Promotion [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 23)
    - Cable: USA Network, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 24)
    - Cameras and Photo Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 25)
    - CBS Radio: Durkee, Cutler, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 26)
    - Charity Accounts [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 27)
    - Cigarette Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 28)
    - Circulation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 29)
    - Circulation: Direct Mail Subscriptions [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 30)
    - Circulation: Weekly Reports, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 31)
    - Clips: Census, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 32)
    - Clips: People, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 33)
    - Clips: Supermarkets, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 34)
    - Clips: Time Inc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 35)
    - College Market, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 36)
    - Commercials, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 37)
    - Comp Lists, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 38)
    - Company Plane, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 39)
    - Complaints: Advertising, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 40)
    - Complaints: Reports, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 41)
    - Condé Nast, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 42)
    - Congress/Complimentary Subscriptions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 43)
    - Conventions: Dinners, Luncheons, Etc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 44)
    - Conventions: Trade, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 45)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Miami, Florida: January 5-8, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 46)
    - Conventions: B'nai B'rith Foundation: Eugene Kummel Award Dinner: January 12, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 47)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: Broadmoor: April 18-21, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 48)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Chicago: May 9-12, 1982 (Offsite-box 2991, Folder 49)
    - Conventions: American Association of Advertising Agencies: Greenbrier: May 12-15, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 1)
    - Conventions: Marines: Washington, D.C.: May 21, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 2)
    - Conventions: National Association of Convenience Stores: Chicago: September 19-23 (Did Not Attend), 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 3)
    - Conventions: Food Management Institute: Reno: October 24-27, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 4)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Advertising Agencies: Scottsdale: October 27-31 (Did Not Attend), 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 5)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 6)
    - Copyright, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 8)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution: Letterpress And Offset [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 9)
    - Cosmopolitan [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 10)
    - Couponing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 11)
    - Covers, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 12)
    - Covers: Other Magazines, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 13)
    - Covers: Test and Research, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 14)
    - CPM [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 15)
    - Delivery Reports: Subscription Newsstands, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 16)
    - Direct Mail, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 17)
    - Direct Mail Response, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 18)
    - Discounts [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 19)
    - Discover, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 20)
    - Distribution, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 21)
    - Dorset Suite #907, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 22)
    - Edit: Close, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 23)
    - Edit: Closing Week for Sales Personnel, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 24)
    - Edit: Color, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 25)
    - Edit: Pages, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 26)
    - Edit: Serious People Articles, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 27)
    - Eighties: Futures [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 28)
    - EPCOT Disney Pavilion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 29)
    - Esquire, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 30)
    - Executive Compensation [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 31)
    - Expense Account: Ageing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 32)
    - Fact Sheets: Marketing Service, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 33)
    - Fast Close, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 34)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 35)
    - Filler Space, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 36)